china-admissions.com 2017-06-28

# Privacy Policy

**Warning** : mysqli_query(): (HY000/1030): Got error 28 from storage engine in **/home/richco6/public_html/china-admissions.com/wp-includes/wp-db.php** on line **1877**

This privacy policy (together with the terms and conditions) sets out the basis on which any personal data we collect from you, or that you provide to us, will be processed by China Admissions. Please read the following carefully to understand our policy regarding your personal data and how we will treat it. China Admissions may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with the changes. This policy is effective from 16th April 2014.

 **What we collect**

We may collect and process the following information about you:

●      Information which you provide to us from any of the input areas within the website.  
●      Information which you provide to us by any other means including (without limitation) telephone, fax or post.  
●      Information which you provide to us in connection with your application, which will be handled in accordance with this privacy policy and our data protection statement, which forms part of the declaration.  
●      If you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence.

 **What we do with the information**

We use personal information held about you in the following ways:

●      to process your application.  
●      to notify you about changes to our service.  
●      to ensure that content from our website is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer.  
●      to keep you informed (with your consent) by electronic means, or other means, of information about specific funding, sponsorship opportunities or services and products that we think may be of interest to you.  
●      to provide you (unless you object) with general information relevant to students.

We may share personal information included in your application, or which you subsequently supply to us, with the staff of the institutions which (i) you have previously or currently attend as a student or (ii) you are making application to attend for further or higher education as indicated in your application. More details of the parties with whom some or all of your information will shared is set out in our data protection statement which forms part of the declaration.

As part of your application, you will be asked if you wish to nominate a representative who may speak to China Admissions on your behalf. You do not have to nominate a representative but where you do so you must have their consent that they will to act as your representative and that we may hold their personal details including their name and contact details. We will only discuss your application, give information or take directions from your nominated representative if you make us aware that you have appointed one.

We may, on occasion, be required to undertake a check of your identity. This will be conducted in confidence. We will normally discuss this with you prior to carrying out any identity checks except as set out in our data protection statement.

China Admissions will cooperate, where it is required to do so, with enquiries from authorities which demonstrate a legal requirement for access to information about you. 

 **Communication**

The information we collect from you in connection with your application will include (without limitation) your name; postal and email address; and telephone numbers, both home and mobile. If any of these details change, it is important that you tell us straight away so that we can communicate with you about your application.

We will normally communicate with you by electronic means in respect of any application made by you.

You may contact us by any of the methods set out on our  **contact us**  page of the website. If you have any questions about our use of your personal data, contact us here.

 **Promotional Information and Suggestions**

In addition, from time to time, we would like to make use of your personal information to send you promotional information about (without limitation) products and services which may be of interest to you. Commercial mailings may include information sent by the China Admissions on behalf of carefully selected third parties; these can include information on accommodation, discounts, tickets, travel, banking, and professional associations. Please note that except as set out in this privacy policy or data protection statement, your details will not be released to any third party.

We may collect information about your computer, including where available your IP address, operating system and browser type, for system administration and to report aggregate information to our advertisers. This is statistical data about our users’ browsing actions and patterns, and does not identify any individual.

You may, at any time, withdraw your permission for China Admissions to use your personal information for the purposes of sending mailings by contacting us.

 **Cookies**

We may collect information about your computer, including where available your IP address, operating system and browser type. This is statistical data about our users’ browsing actions and patterns, and does not identify you as an individual.

China Admissions may use cookies. A cookie is a small amount of data which is stored on your computer and which is revealed to China Admissions when you use this network. China Admissions uses cookies only to make it easier to identify you when using the network. China Admissions does not use cookies to collect additional information about you. You can configure your web browser not to accept cookies.

We use Google Analytics tracking code that supports Display Advertising in order to use Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting so that we can purpose content on our website according to the demographics (such as age, gender and interests) of the visitors to particular pages. You may opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customise Google Display Network ads by using the Ad Settings on Google’s website.

 **Other Websites**  

 The website may contain links that make it easy for you to visit other websites. China Admissions does not have any control over these websites. Therefore, if you use these links to leave China Admissions and visit websites operated by third parties, China Admissions cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information that you provide whilst visiting these websites.

 **Requesting or Amending Information**

You may request for us to provide you with details of personal information that we hold about you by contacting us. There will be a small fee payable.

If you request us to do so we will consider making changes to the information that we hold about you. We will change certain limited information that we hold about you where you tell us it is incorrect.
